Cherry：Do we wait here?
Cherry：ここで待てばいい？
Xenon：Yes. Why did you accompany me here anyway?
Xenon：あぁ それより なんでお前まで来てるんだ
Cherry：Hey, I took part in the Boss fight; make sense that I get to rescue the princess, right? I want to see NEKO in person as well.
Cherry：ボス戦クリアして 姫を助けないなんておかしいじゃん？ それに NEKOちゃんに会いたいし
Xenon：... Princess? I say more pixie than princess.
Xenon：……姫ってなんだ？妖怪の間違いだろ
Cherry：You are so mean~ She's a cute girl. isn't she?
Cherry：最低 可愛い女の子じゃないの？
Xenon：Umm... She's... unique, to say the least. Be prepared when you see her.
Xenon：あぁ…変なやつだよ 心の準備しておけ
Cherry：All this talk is making me even more interested to see her!
Cherry：余計に興味湧いて来ちゃったなぁ
Cherry：On a side note, that's a serious crowd down there at the main entrance.
Cherry：てかさ さっき下のエントランスにめっちゃ人いたね
Cherry：Good thing you had friends that could let us in through the back door. I thought we're gonna get stuck outside.
Cherry：あんたの友達が裏から通してくれてよかった 入れないかと思ったわ
Cherry：Didn't you say that the admins have been watching you closely?
Cherry：あんた管理局に目つけられてんじゃなかった？
Xenon：I still have my connections over here. If not, I wouldn't know any of this in the first place.
Xenon：ある程度は顔が利く そうでなきゃ こんなこと知らない
Cherry：Wow, so a shut-in like you actually made "friends"...
Cherry：コミュ障のくせに友達いたんだ……
Xenon：You... it's all thanks to them that the evidence I provided could actually influence the investigation.
Xenon：おい……あいつらがいたから 俺の掴んだ証拠で 捜査の方向性を変更できたんだぞ
Xenon：... Ah, we should stop chatting here.
Xenon：……ここで話すのはやめよう
[>>>Fast Forward>>>]
[>>>早送り>>>]
Xenon：Hey. Over here.
Xenon：ここだ
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Ehhh? Why are you the one to come and get me? Where are my dad and others?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：えぇ～？なんでXenonがお迎え？パパは？
Xenon： I notify them to wait at home. There are still some procedures to go through.
Xenon：家で待つよう連絡しておいた 手続きがまだ残ってる
Xenon：You probably have no idea why you are released, right?
Xenon：なんで自分が釈放されたか分かってないだろ
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Dude, I don't even know why I was arrested in the first place! It's utterly ridiculous!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：何で捕まったのかも分かんないもん！イミフすぎ！
Xenon：You don't remember, do you...? That makes it even harder to explain things clearly.
Xenon：覚えてないのか……？なら余計に説明しづらいな
NEKO#ΦωΦ：...... Who's that behind you?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：……後ろにいるのは？
Cherry：Hi~
Cherry：こんにちは～
NEKO#ΦωΦ：EHHH!? It's Cherry! OH MY ****** GOD!!!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：え！？Cherryだ！うわわわわ！！
Cherry：Eh? You recognize me?
Cherry：ん？あたしのこと知ってんの？
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Of course! NEKO is a big fan of yours! Why are you here!?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：ファンです！！どうしてここに！？
Xenon：She's half the reason why you could be released.
Xenon：お前を釈放するために協力してもらった
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Huh? What does that mean? Hmm??
NEKO#ΦωΦ：ん？どういうこと？んん？
Xenon：It's a long story... All in all, we should leave here before we get any attention. Let's go.
Xenon：話すと長くなる……とにかく今のうちに出よう 行くぞ
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Come on~ tell me what's going on~
NEKO#ΦωΦ：えぇ～！教えてくれてもいいじゃん！
Xenon：You are so noisy... I'll tell you once we leave here.
Xenon：うるさい……歩きながら話す
Xenon：There's a **** ton of people at the main entrance ready to engulf you. Keep your head down.
Xenon：エントランスのやつらは皆お前を待ってる 目立つなよ
[Signal Lost]
[電波切断]